Right. Here's the bonus. This is just added information. You can skip it if you want,
but this is just a scenario building exercise for any service-based business. I'm going to stick
with just service here. If your business is related to selling products, like a physical,
tangible product, and you've got to deal with lead time, shipping, all of those aspects,
go straight to the product playbook. For this bonus, it's going to be strictly service-based
businesses. You've got $0 starting budget. You're not advertising. You're not paying for software.
There's no virtual assistance you can have. You always have the free version of ChatGPT at your
disposal here, but this is just SWEQUITY. Free tools, right? Two hours per day, obviously 14 hours per
week because we're working on weekends over here. No website required. However you've stumbled onto
my course here, a lot of early onset entrepreneurs get stuck in like, what should I name my business?
What's the LLC? What does my logo look like? You probably, even though I'm like repping it as hard
as I possibly can, it's literally on my chest. As much as I try to promote the logo, you probably
haven't really remembered it, right? So don't necessarily worry about the things that need to be
later on. That's going to be a later on problem. That's like brand remembering. That's further down
the marketing funnel. If you don't know what that is, I recommend you look it up.
You don't even really need a website to make your first sale, okay? But you will need a
way to collect payments. That's a must and there are free versions of that, right? Apple Pay,
Android, Google Pay, whatever that is, crypto, all of these aspects need to happen because if you don't
have that and you stumble through it, you finally got all the way, 95% of the way, and there's no
pay, they're going to, oh, that was all for nothing. You don't know what you're doing. All that
SWEQUITY is lost. You're going to hate yourself for it. So make sure you have that ready.
Let's move on here.
First, understand your offer. I'm going to go with, you build Amazon stores as your service
and you need to find different businesses that may be selling a website or you found them on
Instagram through scrolling and you saw that they had a shitty website and they're non-existent
on Amazon and boom, there's your, there's your audience, right?
What does that offer look like? I'm going to build your Amazon store. Great. Awesome. Let's
niche it down. I'm going to build skincare Amazon stores. I'm going to build, um, you know,
version one of your Amazon store, whatever that looks like. It needs to be a little bit mapped
out. Build the list. Who are you looking for? Understand exactly your niche audience and
literally put, I, I would go way further than 20. I'd go a hundred, right? You want to know exactly
how many it's going to take for you to get that sale. So why are you stopping at 20? Let's up those
numbers here. Um, what am I sending out to each one of these? Is it going to be, you know,
10 are in the skincare sector, 10 are in the, um, uh, apparel sector, 10 more are in selling
Japanese pens, uh, 10 more are selling sunglasses, right? Um, this is still pertaining to my Amazon,
Amazon store service. Um, I'm building out a script for each one of those different brands,
those different verticals and sending it out, right? If in that example, still a hundred different
individuals, um, you know, split up by 10 each by vertical, right? And then send out those messages
however you want. Figure that out. It should happen quickly. If you want to do it in two days,
okay, take your time. If you want to do it in a day, which I'd recommend, do it. All right.
Continuing on with tracking all of this reply to your leads and have that schedule link,
right? If it's a sales call that is necessary, how are they going to book time with you on your
calendar? Is it as simple as a calendar link? Is it a little bit more complicated than you have
different sales, um, team members that are like underneath you, however it looks, what are they
doing to schedule time? And you should have that booked. You should have reminders on, um,
you'll eventually come to the point of like no show appointments. And that's a rather frustrating
journey of like, well, why are they not showing up? Oh, it's because they didn't have reminders on.
Um, did you text them? Did you email them? Um, however you have to, you know, leave a trail of
breadcrumbs to get them to that appointment is going to be its own little mini hurdle discovery on that
call of your Amazon, uh, store building service. What do you need to learn from that? Right. A good
salesman is not saying I built Amazon stores, um, for a living and that's, we're great because,
right. That's not a great presentation for your sale. Your presentation for your sales should be,
tell me about your business. Tell me more about your product. Insert where my service is based on
their future problem. Oh, don't worry so much about getting traction to your website because it's very
difficult to get traction to your website because no one's looking for skincare, um,
rs.com, whatever that random, terrible name for a skincare brand might be. Um,
they're looking for it on Amazon. If they're typing in skincare on Amazon, we're going to help you with
that search engine optimization. We're going to help you, um, build out impressions, which will
furthermore lead those customers back to your website. Okay. So that should be discovery,
diagnose the problem, learn about their business, enter in your solution service as the solution.
Close that deal, man. Close the deals. How many, um, how many first outreaches did it take
to get to close deals? Okay. Um, now you got to do the thing. So you should by now have built the
roadmap, right? Pause it however you feel, uh, if you're going on day one, day two, day three, day four,
day five, whatever. Um, what does that timeline look like for them? They should literally see it in
front of their face, a PDF file. That's always a little difficult because editing on a PDF is a
nightmare, uh, holds separate discussion. Google sheets, week one, week two, week three as rows.
What happens next as columns? Um, did it happen like status as another column, right? Make sure they know,
understand, um, um, cadence of conversations also, right? We're meeting every Wednesday. If you don't
come on Wednesday, then like, what are you doing? You should be here. You paid for the service, be here
on Wednesdays or like, you know, maybe that's a discussion, uh, contractually as well. Um, feedback loop,
you want their review, right? You want to understand what a good job looks like quite literally within
the timeline as well as, um, upsell. What does an upsell look like? What time do you implement that
conversation of an upsell and what customer deserves, uh, necessitates and, um, you know, might just dismiss
the upsell completely mapped out, mapped out, mapped that out, right? Maybe you have different types
of customers. Uh, even if it's within the same niche, you're going to have to deal with the
individual, right? So you'll understand what I mean when I say, you'll know this customer does not want
an upsell. This customer might, it might actually be super beneficial. Um, this customer might need it
at the forefront, right? Um, that feels like day seven to me, but this is now day seven. This is more
of like the debrief. Reply to all non-responders. Don't just send one message and give up. Keep going.
Keep going. Keep going. Give your value as well. Is that a, uh, screenshot of something? Is that, um,
go to my content within Instagram? What does that look like of sharing proof? Do it again. Do it again,
right? Create a new pipeline. And then as always, weekly debrief. Um, this is just understanding that
volume of what it's going to take for you to get that sale. So that funnel that we had talked about
all the way from cold outreach to sale, feel free to just break down your time as well. Um, however you
see fit, but this is just an example, and then just copy paste, whatever you need here, right? Whatever
service of however you want to package it up, here are examples, right? Um, here is your Google business
profile. Um, this is what I do for, um, service-based businesses. It's going to take two hours. Here's a
PDF report and a video for every single client. I build landing pages for a client, right? Uh,
how long is it going to take? What do they need to understand your value, right? All of these things,
build this out your menu, so to speak for your business. What does that conversation look like?
Where can they venture off in, um, you know, the different parts of the sales call? If it's 15
minutes and you don't know what to talk about, you should be asking questions. You should be learning
from them and understanding their pain points and where you can insert your service inside of those pain
points. Payment and onboarding. On the call, you should be sending a sales, uh, a payment link,
right? Easier for them. Hey, can you just confirm that you received it? Take your time to look through
it, but if you can just confirm you've seen it, um, that would help me a lot. That way it doesn't go to
your spam or whatever that sounds like in your sales call.
Debrief. Weekly. This is an important aspect for the founder. If you're not doing this, you're just,
you just have a job, right? What worked? What didn't work? What caused friction in, um, any aspect of this?
What gave you the biggest headache? What software can you use to alleviate that headache? What did you not
expect? Right? So, all of these and
it's going to be a worksheet. It's going to be an exercise for you, but I believe in you.
Whenever you need help, feel free to reach out to me
through my email, through our website, book a calendar time with me.
Um, our time is on the terramor.io website. At that bottom right is our calendar link.
All right. Take care. I'll see you on the next course.